http://www.mcelhanney.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Search:
LOGIN
QUIZ
CONTACT
Linkedin page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowFacebook page opens in new windowInstagram page opens in new window
HomeAboutServices
GeomaticsEngineeringGIS & Remote SensingPlanningLandscape ArchitectureEnvironmental
PortfolioCareers
Career OpportunitiesCultureCareer GrowthStudents & New Graduates
Scope
This policy describes the information collected via McElhanney’s Website and how this information is collected and used.
Personal Information and Consent
All personal information created, held or collected by McElhanney is protected under British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act and McElhanney has developed policies and procedures with respect to the proper collection, use and disclosure of such information.
Specific personal information, such as your name, phone number or email address, is not automatically collected. This type of information would only be obtained if you supplied it to McElhanney by email or by completing any online form or request for service. Supplying your personal information to McElhanney in this manner implies that you consent to McElhanney using that personal information to provide you with the requested service.
Collection of Standard Internet Information
McElhanney uses software programs to monitor network traffic, to measure traffic patterns, to administer our Website and to gather broad demographic information.  These software programs automatically receive and temporarily store information supplied by your browser in McElhanney’s Web server logs.  This is typically anonymous statistical data that is not connected with your personal information.
Links
McElhanney’s Website contains links to other sites.  McElhanney is not responsible for the content, data collection (including the collection of personal information, if any), or the privacy policies of such sites and McElhanney encourages you to examine their individual privacy policies.
Contact Information
Queries or complaints related to the privacy of information collected via McElhanney’s Website can be sent by email to privacy@mcelhanney.com
Go to Top
